<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cv on Gabe Nespoli</title>
    <link>https://www.gabenespoli.com/tags/cv/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cv on Gabe Nespoli</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:47:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gabenespoli.com/tags/cv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabe Nespoli, Ph.D.</title>
      <link>https://www.gabenespoli.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabenespoli.com/about/</guid>
      <description>pdf | cv
Kitchener, Ontario, Canada
 gabenespoli@gmail.com
 linkedin.com/in/gabenespoli
 github.com/gabenespoli
Summary  Resourceful innovator and creative thinker who developed a novel analysis method for assessing localized neural dynamics Experienced programmer with a keen interest in machine learning Superb communication skills and ability to clearly explain complex ideas  Work Experience Knowledge Translator &amp;amp; Mentor as a Data Scientist at Ryerson University | 2018-Present
 Creates software tools for analysis and visualization of biological time-series data, automating many analyses and saving hours of researcher time Creates tutorials and mentors graduate students, inspiring them to learn programming and empowering them to understand and manipulate their data Projects: PHZLAB (github link), Neural Entrainment Toolbox (github link)  Innovator of Advanced Signal Processing Techniques as a Graduate Student at Ryerson University | 2012-2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.gabenespoli.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 12:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gabenespoli.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Gabriel A. Nespoli Curriculum Vitae
resume
Education Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.), Psychology (2018)
Ryerson University, Toronto, Canada
Advisor: Frank A. Russo
Committee: Todd A. Girard, Margaret C. Moulson, Peter Vuust
Dissertation: The neuroscience of groove: Neural mechanisms marrying music and movement
Master of Arts (M.A.), Psychology (2014)
Ryerson University, Toronto, Canada
Advisor: Frank A. Russo
Committee: Benjamin J. Dyson, Lixia Yang
Thesis: Musicianship and neural synchronization at multiple timescales</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>